Jonah! Jonah, my boy!
ヨナ坊…
ヨナ坊ちゃん
I've lost sight of him.
見失っちまったぜ
それはそうだろう
No duh. Jonah's an
ex-woodsman--an alpine soldier!
ヨナ坊は元山男　山岳兵
I was a police officer! A cop!
俺は元警察官だぜ…ケーサツ
Although I was in an anti-terrorist unit...
対テロ部隊だったけどよ
This is a high-pressure gas gun.
高圧ガス銃です
ペイント弾を撃ちだします
It fires paintballs.
They hurt pretty bad when they hit.
当たると結構痛いですよ
I know all about it, Chief.
知ってるよアネゴ
So what? You want me to train with that?
何　それ使って訓練しろって
Damn straight!
その通り
--Lutz, you were the only one to get
hit by enemy fire in that last skirmish!
この間の戦いで敵の弾を頂戴したのは
ルツあなただけですよ
お説教タイムだ
--It's lecture time!
--Lutz, you were the only one to get
hit by enemy fire in that last skirmish!
--Scary!
--Lutz, you were the only one to get
hit by enemy fire in that last skirmish!
怖いっす
So go fight for the flag
with Jonah in the mountains.
ヨナ君と山でフラグ戦をしろってさ
Whoever nabs the flag first wins.
先に旗を取ったほうが勝ちって奴
No, I don't want to shoot Lutz.
いやだよ　ルツと打ち合うなんて
Then how about this, Jonah?
じゃこうしようヨナ
You get 15 points for every time you hit Lutz
ルツに一発当てることに15点
and 30 points if you get the flag first.
先に旗を取れば30点
For every 50 points earned,
50点につき一枚　スペシャル御馳走券をプレゼント
I'll present you with a special meal ticket!
レッツゴー　ヨナ
Let's go, Jonah!
Do that level of math in your head!
それぐらい暗算でやれ
Everyone respects your shooting skills.
お前の射撃の器用さは誰もが認めてる
You just gotta skillfully
walk through mountains, too.
山も器用に歩けってことさ
Commence the operation.
行動開始
Dammit! Everyone was giving me a hard time.
クッソー…皆好き勝手言いやがって
隙だらけだ
He's covered in openings!
どうも頭の中でぐるぐると…
It keeps spinning around in my head.
I can't seem to forget my sniping experiences.
狙撃ってのはなかなか忘れねぇ
Both the times I could shoot
and the times I couldn't...
撃ったことも撃てなかったことも
That hit man from Orchestra...
殺し屋オーケストラ
女子供だからって　撃ってなかった俺はヘタレか
Am I a loser because I couldn't shoot that girl?
俺のスナイピングは人質に銃突きつけているド汚え犯罪者
My sniping is meant for nasty
thugs with guns aimed at hostages
or terrorist scum with their
finger on the bomb's switch.
爆弾のスイッチに指かけてるテロ野郎
そいつらの脳幹をブッ飛ばし
My skills were honed to blow out
their brains and send them to Hell
指をピクリともさせず地獄に落としため磨かれたものだ
before they could even move a finger.
They weren't meant for shooting kids.
決して子供を撃つために使われるもんじゃねぇ
But...
だが…じゃもう一度オーケストラの女みたいなのが現れて
But if another girl like
the one from Orchestra shows up
and the Little Lady is in a pinch,
how would I normally handle that?
お嬢がピンチになった時 俺はどうするんだよってなるような普通
Could I shoot her?
Make that split-second decision?
撃てるのか そいつを一瞬で判断して
I probably could.
撃つんだろう なんせお嬢は俺の雇い主
After all, the Little Lady is
my employer. I even respect her.
尊敬だってしてる
But what if the attacker looked just like Jonah?
じゃあそいつがヨナ坊にそっくりな奴だったら
Jonah!
ヨッナツ坊
Wait, dammit!
待ちあがれ　こら
Sweet! I'm catching up!
よっしゃ…追いつくぜ
Youch!
Wh-What?! I got nailed by a paint ball!
なっなに？
しっかりペイント弾
Th-There he is!
で　出た
One, two, three, four, five,
一二三四五六七八…
全く期待を裏切らないなルツは
--I swear, you never betray my expectations, Lutz!
--six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Fine, fine! I'll take the training seriously!
ハイハイ
ちゃんと訓練します
次からしっかりしますから
--I'll take it seriously next time!
--Lame!
たっせぇ
Tensions are still high due to territory problems
領土問題で緊張が続く中東A国とヨーロッパB国に衝撃が始めました
between Middle Eastern Country A
and European Country B.
An international communications company
reported that Country A's military
両国の停戦ラインにA国陸軍の部隊が集結していると…
--is gathering around the line
of control bordering the two nations.
国際通信情報社が公表したのです
--Valmet, wake up and get ready to go.
--is gathering around the line
of control bordering the two nations.
バルメ 起きて準備して
Good morning, Koko!
おはようございます　ココ
Isn't our agenda today to attend that meeting?
今日の予定は顔合わせですね
Yes!
イェース
Country B's embassy in London is holding
場所はロンドン
B国大使館
a UAV "Unmanned Aerial
Vehicle Supply Committee."
UAV無人航空機導入調達委員会
当委員会は
This committee is dedicated to introducing
我が国の陸空軍への無人航空機導入を審理するものであります
unmanned aerial vehicles to
Country B's Army Air Forces.
We will be looking at HCLI's
American-made Predator
HCLI様の米製ブレデターとユーロ・グループ様のニューロン計画
and the Euro Group's nEUROn Project.
--We would like to hold fair negotiations
--The competition brought out a real doozy.
最終決議へ向け公正なる交渉を行いたいと考えております
向こうさ　スゴイのを送り込んできた
--before deciding who to go with.
--The competition brought out a real dozy.
--Wow!
Amalia Torohovsky, the former
actress and active arms dealer.
アマーリア・トロホブスキー
元女優の兵器ブローカー
スッゴイ美人じゃ
She's way pretty!
Koko Hekmatyar! Oh, my! My goodness!
ココ・ヘクマティアルさん
とっても若くてかわいらしいディーラーさんがいるって聞いてと
I heard that a remarkably young
and cute dealer would be here,
どうしても気になってきちゃたんですよ
so I just had to come check you out!
My, the rumors are true!
Please go easy on me.
あら…ホントだわ
おてやわらかにねぇ…
S-Sure...
は　はー
We have always stood on the borderland.
I'm enjoying the view from here.
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe...
Eeny,meeny,miny,moe...
much the same
We have always stood on the borderland.
日听   猫日和
I'm enjoying the view from here.
日听      框框
神
岛
&
诸
恶
魔
Pike or shield?
Pike or shield?  負けたくはない　でも傷つけたくもない
Maketaku wa nai demo kizu tsuketaku mo nai
校对   YAYA
手に取って　確かめてた
Te ni totte tashikameteta
Kitto modorenain datte
きっと戻れないんだって
Whose side are you on?
翻译  TL旧民
(Don't want to know!) Omoide wa kase
Don't want to know!  思い出は枷
时轴  野田酱
(Don't want to know!) Atozuke no love
Don't want to know!  後付けのlove
(Don't want to know!) Yasashisa wa ada
Don't want to know!  優しさは仇
We have always stood on the borderland.
后期  aoi
Hirogeru ryoute keep balance
広げる両手　keep balance
Yori takaku toberu hou he
より高く飛べる方へ
Mamoritai yo
守りたいよ 僕らの翼のないこの背中に背負った
Bokura no tsubasa no nai kono senaka ni seotta
Reality and Dream
Reality & Dream
This stinks! It stinks big! Listen to this, Jonah!
まぁ　参った参った
聞いてよヨナ
I doubt telling me will make things any better.
僕は聞いてもどうにもならないと思うけどね
That's okay, that's okay.
いいのいいの
"Mondo Grosso"
Our opponent this time is mighty formidable.
かなりやるよ　今回の相手
It's like, the deal was already
made by the time I arrived.
私が行ったところで「もう話はすんじゃってますよ」状態
It's like, "Everyone here is my prisoner."
「この場の全員は私のトリコ」状態なんだよ
Just as the rumors claimed,
that lady is quick at pulling her strings.
噂通りすごい根回しの速さだ　あのおばさん
--A lady?
--Right!
おばさん？
そう
She's a super-hot former stage actress!
舞台女優だった　超美人だよ
If she said, "Buy my weapons!"
あんなのが「武器買って」ってきたら
all those old military elites
would buy them in a heartbeat.
たちまち軍人の偉いおじさんたちが落ちちゃうなぁ
She was a celebrity and married
a wealthy man, but then he passed away.
もともとセリフだったのに
資産家と結婚してすぐに先立たれて
And wham! His fortune all went to her.
その遺産がドドーンと彼女に
She made good use of her
arms-related inheritance and connections.
その中の武器関連の資産と人脈を彼女は駆使した
At any rate,
Amalia Torohovsky was one weird lady.
それにしても アマーリア・トロホブスキー
変な人だった
What are you trying to sell this time?
今度は何を売ろうというんだ
Unmanned aerial vehicles.
無人航空機
They are radio-controlled
planes equipped with radar.
ラジコン飛行機にレーダーを載せ
They're used for reconnaissance and scouting.
偵察斥候を行う
They don't get tired or careless.
疲れたり気を抜いたりしない
No one dies if one gets shot down.
撃墜されても人が死なない
Equip it with weapons and
you can even use it for battle.
武装して戦闘も可能
Just recently, one of these blew up
an organization's executive officers.
つい最近某組織の幹部をこれが爆殺した
So we've hit the age where robots kill humans.
ロポットが人を殺す時代が来たということだ
Isaac Asimov might cry if he saw one of these.
アシモフが見たら泣いちゃうかもしれない
I don't get that, but I'm not so sure about those...
よくわからないけど　なんだかな
Oh, I'm with you!
I'm not sure about those things...
あっそれ私も一緒 何だかね
まぁ…それが売んなきゃいけないのが私の仕事のわけだった
But it's my job to sell those puppies.
Koko!
ココちゃん
Isn't this country hot?
The skies are gray and the food stinks.
暑いねこの国
空気がドンヨリしてるし ご飯もあんまりおいしくないっす
Now, now!
まぁまぁ
So, about those American-made
Predators you want...
んて　お望みの米製プレデターですが
The Americans aren't hot on the idea at all.
アメリカさんぜんっぜん乗り気じゃないっす
If America went along with your idea
今回の案件って
中東A国に民族問題を穏便におさめるってことを条件に
and sold the UAVs to Middle Eastern
Country A under the condition
that they must peacefully
resolve their civil problems,
アメリカがUAV売ったら
neighboring Country B
would throw a major hissy fit!
今度は隣りのB国がモーレツに反発しちゃって
Then they'd have to offer
to sell some to Country B, too.
それじゃB国にも売るよって
Isn't that totally like putting out a fire?
火消の意味が強いじゃない
In all reality, Country B would suddenly remember
本当のことは
Ｂ国がニューロン計画で
自分らもUAV作りに参加してたのを思い出して…
that they're developing their own
UAVs with the nEUROn Project.
If that puts the fire out naturally,
then all is okey-dokey!
自然鎮火してくれたなら まぁOKみたいな　ね
The UAV market is going to
burn even hotter than before.
UAV市場はこれからさらに燃え上がる
"I wish I made better scaffolding,"
is a lame thing to say once it's too late.
後になって
もっと足場を組んでおけばよかったなんてマヌケのセリフだ
Well, it's about time I left.
それじゃそろそろ
Scarecrow'll have a cow if
I hang out with you too much.
あんまにココちゃんとくっつくとスケアクロウがうるさいっす
What?! What is it?
えっなになに…
So the technician working with the CIA
chose to go after me with Scarecrow...
スケアクロウと一緒に私を付け回すことを選択したんだね
CIA付きの技術屋さん
This means you may
cross various bridges with me,
ってことは私と一緒にいろんな橋を渡るかもってことだよ
not that I'll stop you.
止めはしないけど
C-Could this be a...
ん？これはもしや…
...d-d-d-d-diamond?!
ダッダダ…イヤ
Wow, this rocks!
ウワ…スッゲ
Keep the Americans under check
so they don't pull away from this affair.
アメリカがこの件から勝手に手を引かないように
牽制し続けろ　いいね
Got it?
This is kinda sketchy.
I feel like she's totally using me.
なんかヤバいかも
いい感じに使われちゃってる気がするっす
But hey, that's cool.
でもまぁ…いいか…
Run by the hotels accommodating
Country B's bigwigs, Ugo.
B国の幹部がいるロンドン中のホテルを巡るよ　ウゴ
Roger.
了解
Okay! Let's sell away!
よーっし…いっちょ売ったるかー
Hm? The Little Lady is on fire!
おっノリノリだぜお嬢
Aren't you Miss Hekmatyar of HCLI?
HCLI　ヘクマティアル様ですね
Please wait in the lobby.
ロビーに居てお待ちください
General?
将軍
Miss Hekmatyar!
ミス・ヘクマティアル
Well, you can see how things
stand this time around. Sorry.
今回はこういう事なんて…ごめんね
I am most sorry, Miss Hekmatyar.
大変申し訳ございません ミス・ヘクマティアル
This is definitely your scheduled meeting time,
but the Colonel is currently out.
確かに約束のお時間ですが
大佐は外出しておりまして
Yikes!
--I am sorry, but the Lt. General
expedited his plans and left.
申し訳ありません 中将は予定を早められ
すでに空港へ
--Yikes!
--I am sorry, but the Lt. General
expedited his plans and left.
I was originally on the side
pushing for the Predators,
私はプレデター導入賛成派だったんだけども
but the Euro Group won me over.
ユーロ・グループに説得されちゃって…
Euro armament should use Euro technology.
ユーロの軍備は　ユーロの技術で…
Yikes!
I see her shadow no matter where I go!
どこに行っても彼女の影が…
That's one amazing position
the Little Lady is twisting into.
お嬢がスゲェ形にねじれてるぞ
It surpasses The Thinker.
「考える人」を超えてるぜ
We've got one place left. Let's go, Ugo.
もう一件だ　出して　ウゴ
Who is it?
お相手は
Lieutenant Colonel Marquis
from Country B's army.
陸軍のマリキス中佐
He's done work with us several times in the past.
うちと何度か仕事をした事がある
He's on the side promoting our Predators.
プレデター推進派の方だ
Ms. Torohovsky paid me a visit as well.
私のところにもきたけどね トロホブスキーさん
I have withheld making a decision.
回答は保留にしてあるよ
Thank you very much!
ありがとうございます
But don't you think she is
trying to finish you off quickly
しかし彼女もあなたの実力を恐れて
because she fears your prowess?
速攻でかたをつけようとしているのでは
I imagine HCLI's headquarters
has already informed you,
HCLI本部から聞いてると思うが
貴方の輸入プランはイタリアの新聞に暴露されてしまった
but an Italian newspaper has
exposed your importation plan.
The newspaper is really just a tabloid.
新聞といってもタブロイド紙ですけどね
If she doesn't pull back after this,
これで引かないようなら
一般紙にリークしてトドメをさします
I will leak this information to
a normal paper and finish her off.
Koko was really using her head.
ココちゃんはよく考えたものね
She "acquired Predators that
the Italian air force disposed of"
プレデターをイタリア空軍の払い下げにして
and insisted that America
"would not directly provide the aircrafts."
アメリカの立場直接供与ではないと強調しつつ
She would help Country A save face by
making it look like civilians made the deal.
A国の面子を立てる民間取引の形にしたのね
Hekmatyar's strengths lie in her light footwork.
ヘクマティアルの強みはフットワークの軽さです
Amalia, your connections
and wit proved to be superior.
アマーリアの人脈と機転がそれを上回ったのです
Doesn't the Little Lady
look kinda good in that pose?
なんかお嬢って あのポース似合うよな
To me she looks like she's devising
an incredible plan rather than giving up.
でもなんか諦めっつーより
スゲェ案を考えてそうな気がするぜ
Oh, you said it!
おっいうね
Is our work done, Koko?
仕事は終わり？ココ
Of course not!
まさか
I've passed along all of
the info I was supposed to.
私が語るべき情報はすべて流れた
Now to outwit that lady! That's all I can do.
後は…
裏をかく これしかない
And that is how I fight.
そしてそれが私の戦い方だよ
Is she going to be okay?
大丈夫かよ
We're just leaving Chief,
Wilee, and Lutz here in England.
イギリスにはアネゴとワイリとルツだけってさ
I'm not particularly concerned.
別段不安がねえけど
Let's just get our own jobs done.
俺たちは俺たちの任務をやろうぜ
We can't let our guards down, either.
こっちだって気が抜けないぞ
Guys from the Euro Group are already trailing us.
尾行されてんだぜ ユーログループの方々に
Seriously?!
マージで
She'll be fine with those three.
3人いりゃ大丈夫だろう
You should believe in your comrades' abilities.
仲間の実力ってのは信用するもんだぜ
In short, it'll all end a-okay if
I strike a deal with Country B right quick.
要するに俺がさっさとB国との交渉をまとめちまったら
万事OKっつーことだろう
Nope, nope, that's not happening.
無理無理　そりゃ無理だ
Not when even Koko is having a tough time.
ココでも手こずってるのによ
She's been like this ever since
those negotiations two days ago.
交渉初日から二日間
ずっとあんな感じ
I'm a wee bit worried.
ちょびっとだけ心配です
Koko, you'll get fat if you pig out
on snacks and don't exercise.
ココ
運動しないでお菓子ばかり
肥っちゃいますよ
I wonder if I could make it all go
to my boobs so they're like yours.
胸だけバルメ並みにふくよかになる方法はないだろうか
No! Koko, you're perfect just the way you are!
いいえ　ココはそのままがちょうどいいんです
もん　何言ってんだか
Oh, you're so silly!
She sent another e-mail.
又メール送信です
She has sent 25 e-mails in one hour.
一時間に25発撃ちました
Could we crack them if
we received assistance from
フランス対外治安総局の協力を得ても解読できないか
France's General Directorate
for External Security?
The DGSE?
DGSEですか
I believe so, but I am afraid it
would take a massive amount of time.
確かにできますが　おそらく膨大な時間がかかるかと…
Why worry when we've already basically won?
そんなに心配しなくても我々の勝ちでは
There is nothing HCLI can do now.
HCLIはも手も足も出ないですよ
Ask Amalia for her thoughts on this.
Continue to intercept her messages.
アマーリアに判断を仰ぐ
傍受を続けろ
Hello, Schokolade?
It's no good! No good at all!
もしもーし ショコラーデ
ダメ全然ダメ
I've lost this UAV sales campaign.
今回のUAV売り込み戦 私の負け
My plan was to send the
Predators to Country B via Italy
隣りのA国を刺激しないように
プレデターをイタリア経由でB国に流す私のプラン
to avoid provoking Country A.
It sucked that the Italian
mass media caught wind about my plan.
イタリアのマスコミにバレちゃったら マズかったよ
Ms. Torohovsky had to have used her connections!
あれてトロホブスキーさんのコネクションでしょう　絶対
There is nothing left for me to do.
あれで身動き取れなくなった
HCLI is going to pull out of this game,
わがHCLIは本件から手を引く
although I'll still drop by to
say, "Hi," at tomorrow's vote.
明日の決議には挨拶ぐらいはするけどね…
I just remembered why
女優業をやめる時それほど悩まなかったのを今思い出したわ
it wasn't terribly hard for me
to leave behind my acting career.
Theatre and films are art if you hone your skills.
舞台も映画も極めれば芸術
It is a wonderful world
worth dedicating your life to.
命をかける価値がある素晴らしい世界
But no matter how hard you work,
it will always be empty.
でもどれほど頑張っても虚構
That is how my eyes perceived it.
私の目もそう映ってしまったの　向いてなかったのね
I wasn't cut out for the arts.
At the same time, I discovered this world,
同時に利益のために
騙し騙され演技がバレれば
where you deceive and are
deceived, all for personal gain.
身を切らなければならない
You will pay if people see through your ploys.
そういう世界の存在にも気づいてうたんだわ
Here is what I think:
私はこう判断します
Koko is "acting" during those phone calls
we've been tapping into for the past three days.
この三日間盗聴しつつけたココちゃんの電話は演技
Right, everything is...
そう　すべてが…
...a lie!
嘘です
I thought you really had given up!
私は本当に諦めてしまったのがと…
It's to throw them off. I hope it works.
かく乱だよ
効いてるといいけど
And after a whole bunch of BS,
she sends me a legit e-mail.
そうして散々無駄話した後
本命のメールがくるんっす
Why must everyone around
me be such slave drivers?
どうしてこう私の周りには人使いの荒い…
A single diamond isn't worth all this work!
ダイヤ一個の報酬じゃ足りないっす
In the end, we still don't
know who that woman truly is.
結局この女の子の正体もわからないまま
Koko is preparing to make a massive attack.
ココちゃんは何か大きな一撃の準備をしている
She's trying to tear apart my alliances.
私の包囲網を食い破ろうというのね
That fighting style seems suiting for her.
実にあの娘らしい戦いかただわ
I'll need to remind the executives from
Country B not to change their minds,
何があっても考えを変えないよう
B国幹部たちに念を押す必要があるわね
regardless of what happens.
Little Lady, may I come in?
お嬢　いいか
Sure, Lutz.
いいよ　ルツ
Did you see the TV?
テレビ見たか
Country A dropped the campaign
that America was going after it over.
アメリカが止めにかかったA国の軍事行動が止まったなあ
It seemed a lot like that one idea
of yours. Plus it's mighty timely.
なんかお嬢のかかえてる案件っぼくて
タイムリーかと思ってよ
Armies aren't pushovers that
you can manipulate from bed.
ベットの上で変化を起こせるほど軍って軽くないよ
My idea was just a cog.
私の案件はたった一つの歯車
It takes thousands upon thousands
of those cogs to make an army.
それが何万何億と組み合わさって軍を成す
The complex, grotesque hearts of the people
軍を動かすのは軍を包む複雑怪奇な人々の心
who engulf the army are what make it move.
The world is ignited by people's hearts.
世界は人の心で点火する
Ms. Torohovsky, you're a perfectionist, aren't you?
完璧主義なんですなぁ
トロホブスキーさんは
You have basically been declared the winner.
しかし軍配は貴方に上がったも同然だ
There is no need to try
winning me over anymore, is there?
もはや私を取り込む必要はないじゃないですか
Pardon me, Lieutenant Colonel.
失礼いたします中佐
Please read this.
こちらをご覧ください
うん？これは…
That's--!
Lt. Colonel Marquis?
マリキス中佐
The German air force is purchasing
Predators from America.
ドイツ空軍がアメリカからプレデターを機体輸入します
その数20機
A whole 20 of them!
They are equipped with
German-made ISR systems.
ドイツ製ISRレーダーと組み合わせて運用されます
私はヘクマティアルさんと交渉しにいかなければ
I must go cut a deal with Ms. Hekmatyar.
申し訳ない このへんで失礼させていただきますよ
I'm sorry, but I must take my leave.
Here it comes!
Hekmatyar is launching her attack.
来たヘクマティアルの攻撃
あー終わった
Done at last! My shoulders ache!
肩こったっす
Although all I did was carry contracts
ココちゃんとコネのある軍人に契約書運んで回るだけの仕事っすけど
to various officers Koko has connections with.
おっこの匂いは何
What's that smell?
Sausage from its motherland?!
本場ソーセージ
The beer is black! That looks delicious!
ビールが黒い　おいしそうー
至急　ユーログループの幹部を集めて
Gather the Euro Group's
executive committee immediately.
アマーリア スペインがプレデターを買ったと
Amalia, Spain's army has
purchased some Predators.
Spain as well?
スペインも
Executive Director Nassos of the EAE?
EAE社ナッソス専務
She got me bad, dammit!
やられたぜ畜生
あの小娘のしわざだ
This is all that waif's doing!
俺は今すぐ国に帰らなきゃならねぇ
I must return to my country immediately.
専務　一体何か
Director, what happened?
TOBだ
TOB! Someone is buying up my company's stock.
うちの株がどんどん買われてる
It's some new booming bank
investor called Euro Hekmat-IB!
ユーロ・ヘクマトIBとかいう新興投資銀行だ
違法すれすれ強引さだ　なめやがって
--Her assertiveness is practically illegal!
--Is she trying to tear me apart
rather than tear through my web?
--She's making a fool of me!
--Is she trying to tear me apart
rather than tear through my web?
包囲を食い破るどころか
--Is she trying to tear me apart
rather than tear through my web?
我々をは咬み殺すつもりか
This... This is Koko Hekmatyar!
これが　これがココ・ヘクマティアル
Could we get together and talk, Koko?
合ってお話できないかしら
ココちゃん
Right now.
今から
Sure thing.
いいですよ
I'm sorry to call you out, Koko.
呼び出しちゃってごめんなさいねココちゃん
I'm grateful that you were willing to come.
応じて下さったことに感謝します
Don't worry about it.
お気になさらないでください
By the way, you'll have to
pardon me, but are you armed?
ところで失礼ですが
武装はされていますか
Did you set up some snipers?
狙撃手を配備しているとか
Snipers?
狙撃？
He has a gun on him.
彼は銃を持ってます
On top of serving as a consultant,
he is also my bodyguard.
コンサルタントのほかに 私のボディーガードもしてくれているの
Really! I have no intentions of
hurting you, so please rest at ease.
そんな　あなたにひどいめ見せてやるなんてつもりはないから
安心してください
Should anyone suspicious show up,
we will take appropriate measures.
不審者が現れる際には当方もそれなりの対処をしますよし
As such, I must refuse your request.
予めお断り申し上げます
もう堅い　かたいわぁココちゃん
My! You're so uptight! You're uptight, Koko!
I wouldn't be so sure.
どうだかな
After all, she has some snipers here.
だっているじゃん スナイパー
No, that lady really may not know.
いや　本当にあのおばさんは知らんのかもなぁ
Bearing that in mind, the information
Lehm gave us makes sense.
そう考えるとレーム達の情報も納得なんでな
"When Country B's honcho left England,
he hired some pro thugs."
B国幹部がイギリスを去る時 荒事専門を雇った
The guy who runs the company Koko attacked
just so happens to have a short temper.
ココさんが株式を攻撃した相手が
たまたま血の気の多い奴だったんだな
So he's like, "We'll shoot if
you don't do as we ask," eh?
いうこと聞かなきゃ撃っちゃうぞってことか
Aren't our anti-infrared getups hot?
っつか対赤外線スーツ暑くねぇ
Dude, you guys are wide open times two!
はい丸見えかけ２
I mean, they're keeping
their fingers on the trigger.
何したって　トリガー指がかかりっぱなしだぜ
It's not like we've been hiding up here
for three days. Bucker up and deal.
三日間待ち伏せってわけじゃない 我慢だぜ
When we first met, I should have paid
closer attention to you and noticed
出逢った時にもっとあなたを見て気づいておくべきでした
that the face on the arms dealer
Koko Hekmatyar is a mask.
武器商人ココ・ヘクマティアルの顔は
仮面だわ
Yeah, basically.
ええまあ
Going by that, I guess you
saw right through my diversions.
その様子だと 私のかく乱工作もバレバレでしたか
さすか元女優のトロホブスキーさん
Just what I'd expect of the
former actress, Ms. Torohovsky!
Or so I'd like to say,
but the very first time I saw you,
と言いたいところですが
私は一目であなたが戦場を歩いたことがない商人だと気づきました
I realized that you've never
walked through the battlefield.
武器商人たるもの戦場を歩け
I won't say anything grand like,
"Arms dealers must walk through the battlefield!"
なんてデカイことは言いません
But weapons are what soldiers use in battles.
でも武器とは戦場で兵隊が使うものである
その使われる様をその目で見ていないということは
If you don't see them use your wares,
自分が何を売っているのかわかっていないのと同然
I believe that you essentially
don't know what you're peddling.
と私は考えます
Our wares? I know that
they are "very dangerous."
私達の商品とは
知ってます とても危ないものだわ
"The boss should always be smiling."
ボスってのは常に笑っているべき
Those are the words of
one of my former subordinates.
これはかつての部下の言葉
"Don an iron mask for your
face and armor for your heart."
顔に鉄仮面を心に鎧をまとえ
That is my father's favorite phrase.
これは父の口癖
I follow their advice because
I think they're absolutely right.
その通りだなぁと思って守っています
After all, your heart begins to rot
as you sell weapons on the battlefield.
なぜなら　戦場で武器を売り歩くと
たちまち心が腐る
It's just like how cotton rots in
a jungle even as you're wearing it.
ジャングルで綿の服が着ながらに腐り落ちるように
A place is thrown into pandemonium when
two arms dealers come face to face.
武器商人が二人顔を合わせれば そこはもう修羅場
ボディーガード一人で乗り込むような甘ちゃんは
Are you telling a naïve fool
who only brings one bodyguard
to pull back before she gets burned?
火傷しないうちに引っ込みな
ってことかしら
No, I'm not saying that.
いいえ　そうは言いません
But I have another opinion to share.
ですが更なる意見があります
楽しい　楽しいわ　ココちゃん
This is fun! This is so much fun, Koko!
I don't want you to think I'm strange,
but I've been tingling with excitement
変な人だと思われたくないですけど
ココちゃんの攻撃を受けて
EAE社の方がお国に飛んで帰られたのを目の当りにしてから
ever since I saw the head of the EAE
rush back home after taking your blow!
私　ワクワクしっぱなしで
It's not like I have any strong ideals or beliefs.
強い主義主張や修行があるわけじゃない
I don't have any kids, either. It's not
like I want to earn money for my family.
子供もいない
家族のためにお金を稼ぎたいわけでもない
It's unusual these days for someone
who throws a strong punch to show up.
今時珍しく腰の入ったパンチを打つ商売相手が現れ
And to think it's a girl!
それも女の子
It's fun getting to meet and chat with you.
会って話してみる
楽しい
That alone is reason
enough for me to sell weapons.
私が武器を売る理由は それで十分だわ
今回のUAV受注争奪戦
We shall pull out of this UAV sales campaign.
我々は手を引きましょう
The Euro Group has lost this time around, Koko.
私達ユーログループの負けです ココちゃん
苦戦しました
It was a tough battle!
"Yesterday's enemy is today's friend."
昨日の敵は今日の友
That is how Europeans do things.
それがヨーロッパ人のやり方よ
Here it comes!
来た
昨日の敵は今日の友
"Yesterday's enemy is today's friend."
それがヨーロッパ人のやり方なの
That is how Europeans do things.
二回言われなくてもわかります
You don't have to say it twice!
What do you need?
御用件はなんでしょう
EAE社の株　なんとかしてください お願い
Please do something about EAE's stock. Please!
I figured. But it's not going to be that simple.
やっぱり
でもそうは問屋がおろしませんよ
ここで先の話の続きにつながります
This connects with that
discussion we had a minute ago.
I am well aware of how Europeans do things.
ヨーロッパ的なやり形重々承知しています
しかし考えなおす時代が来たのかもしれませんよ
But it may be time for you
to reconsider your methods.
まず鉄仮面をかぶり釘でもナイフでも刺しておかねばならないのは
We must first don our iron masks
and stab or impale what?
Right. Former national defense-related
companies that have gone private.
そう　次々と民営化が進む元国営防衛関連事業
They will only serve to
hold the whole group back.
彼らは着実にグループ戦略の足をびっぱるだけの存在なってきます
Just like they did this time.
現に今回だって
The feeling that they are an unsinkable warship
国に守られた不沈戦艦根性は
protected by the country
isn't going to vanish over night.
今日明日で消えるものではありません
Inversely, that will--
逆にそれは私達にとって…
Could you sell the stock back at
2.5% of your TOB purchase price?
TOB価格2.5％上乗せで買い戻させてあげてくれますか
人の話聞いてますか
Were you even listening?
The best I can offer is 10%.
最低10％
Five percent!
5%
信じられない
I-I can't believe it!
What's with those women?
何なのあの人達
我がEAE社の生命線の行く末を
They are casually deciding
the fate of the entire EAE!
立ち話で決めようとしちゃってるわけ
Sniper 1, Sniper 2, do you copy?
スナイパー１・２聞こえますか
It-It's about time!
そっ　そろそろ出ます
--Roger!
ラジャ
Koko!
ココ
Fire! Fire!
ファイア　ファイア
Nice shots, Lutz.
ナイスショット　ルツ
They're sprouting little flowers! It's amazing.
奴等花咲かせてる
スゲェ やっぱたいした腕だぜ　ルツ
You really are good, Lutz.
The 270m distance across the
river really isn't that impressive.
川幅270メートルなんてたいした距離じゃねぇ
Lehm could have gotten it done quicker.
レームのおっさんならもっと速くやる
Sorry to startle you.
We merely eliminated some troublemakers.
驚かせてすみません
邪魔を排除しただけです
We didn't kill them.
殺してもいません
Ms. Torohovsky, I'd be
willing to transfer them to you.
トロホブスキーさん
貴方なら譲渡してもいい
How does 5% sound?
5％上乗せでいかがでしょう
I would love to accept that offer.
ぜひお引き受けいたします
Well, I'll see you at the embassy tomorrow.
それでは明日　大使館でお会いしましょう
Jeez! Why were you so soft on that lady?
もうココはなぜあのおばさんに甘いんですか
そう
I was?
Maybe because she said
it's fun talking with me.
私と話すの楽しいって言ってくれたからな
Then I get to have several times more fun!
だったら私はその数億倍は楽しい思いしてますね
Look forward when you drive, Valmet!
前見て運転してバルメ
いや　手こずった　トロホブスキーさん
Man, Ms. Torohovsky was a handful!
If possible, I'd rather not
butt heads with her again.
出来ればもうやり合いたくない相手だよ
But you always run into people
like her again somewhere.
そういう人間に限って 又どこかで出くわすんだな
これが　奇妙なことだ この広い世界で
It's puzzling, considering how big our world is.
Hikari yokotaeru wadatsumi
光横たえる海神
光怪陸離的海底龍神
Soukon no ma ni yurameku ayamachi
創痕の間に揺らめく過ち
累累創痕之間搖曳著縷縷罪孽
Fujou shite iki wo tsugi
浮上して息を継ぎ
浮出水面 吸清吐濁
溶かされ混じるだけの憎愛を手にした
愛與恨 如漆似膠 如影隨形
Tokasare majiru dake no zouai wo te ni shita
Mujun haramu
矛盾孕む
矛盾誕生
Kono sekai goto
この世界ごと 覆い尽くしてる策動の音に傾く夢
冥冥的夢中 世界漸漸傾浸於欺言詭語之中
Ooitsukushiteru sakudou no ne ni katamuku yume
Ashi wa mou nai
脚は　もう無い
足膝 已沒入虛無
Suiheki wo tsuranuku kodou
水壁を貫く鼓動
透過水壁 傳來陣陣鼓動..
恶魔岛字幕组(bbs.emland.net)
诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)
Dragon Shooter phase.1
本字幕由   恶魔岛字幕组   &   诸神字幕组   联合制作
(bbs.emland.net)    (kamigami.org)
日听 猫日和        日听 框框
翻译 TL旧民        校对 YAYA
后期 aoi           时轴 野田
仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
诸神字幕组
恶魔岛字幕组
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"